export const quiz = {
    heading: 'India - State/Capital Quiz',
    quiz: [
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Gujarat?',
            options: ['Ahemdabad', 'Gandhinagar', 'Surat', 'Bhuj'],
            correctAnswer: 'Gandhinagar'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Madhya Pradesh?',
            options: ['Indore', 'Rewari', 'Bhopal', 'Ranchi'],
            correctAnswer: 'Bhopal'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Nagaland?',
            options: ['Shilong', 'Itanagar', 'Kohima', 'Chandigadh'],
            correctAnswer: 'Kohima'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Jharkhand?',
            options: ['Hyderabad', 'Hazaribag', 'Bokaro', 'Ranchi'],
            correctAnswer: 'Ranchi'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Uttarakhand?',
            options: ['Lucknow', 'Dehradun', 'Agartala', 'Shimla'],
            correctAnswer: 'Dehradun'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Himachal Pradesh?',
            options: ['Shilong', 'Ranchi', 'Shimla', 'Raipur'],
            correctAnswer: 'Shimla'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Chattisgadh?',
            options: ['Dispur', 'Bhopal', 'Patna', 'Raipur'],
            correctAnswer: 'Raipur'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Tripura?',
            options: ['Agartala', 'Aizawl', 'Imphal', 'Dispur'],
            correctAnswer: 'Agartala'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Maharashtra?',
            options: ['Bombay', 'Pune', 'Mumbai', 'Nasik'],
            correctAnswer: 'Mumbai'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Rajasthan?',
            options: ['Udaypur', 'Jaisalmer', 'Jaipur', 'Kota'],
            correctAnswer: 'Jaipur'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Tamilndu?',
            options: ['Chennai', 'Ooty', 'Madurai', 'Vellore'],
            correctAnswer: 'Chennai'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Arunachal Pradesh?',
            options: ['Itanagar', 'Imphal', 'Tripura', 'Mizoram'],
            correctAnswer: 'Itanagar'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Punjab?',
            options: ['Moga', 'Chandigadh', 'Amritsar', 'Gurdaspur'],
            correctAnswer: 'Chandigadh'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Odisha?',
            options: ['Koraput', 'Patna', 'Kalahandi', 'Bhubaneshwar'],
            correctAnswer: 'Bhubaneshwar'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Andhra Pradesh?',
            options: ['Amravati', 'Hyderabad', 'Telanagana', 'Vizag'],
            correctAnswer: 'Amravati'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Kerala?',
            options: ['Thiruanantpuram', 'Waynad', 'Kannur', 'Kozhikode'],
            correctAnswer: 'Thiruanantpuram'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Goa?',
            options: ['Ranchi', 'Panaji', 'Vasco d gama', 'Mumbai'],
            correctAnswer: 'Panaji'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Karnataka?',
            options: ['Mysore', 'Bengaluru', 'Dharwad', 'Ballary'],
            correctAnswer: 'Bengaluru'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Manipur?',
            options: ['Imphal', 'Itanagar', 'Kamjong', 'Chandel'],
            correctAnswer: 'Imphal'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Meghalaya?',
            options: ['Darjeeling', 'Shilong', 'Cherrapunji', 'Dawki'],
            correctAnswer: 'Shilong'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of West Bengal?',
            options: ['Howrah', 'Malda', 'Kolkata', 'Purulia'],
            correctAnswer: 'Kolkata'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Haryana?',
            options: ['Chandigadh', 'Ambala', 'Faridabad', 'Panchkula'],
            correctAnswer: 'Chandigadh'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Telangana?',
            options: ['Jangaon', 'Medal', 'Hyderabad', 'Karimnagar'],
            correctAnswer: 'Hyderabad'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Uttar Pradesh?',
            options: ['Lucknow', 'Mirzapur', 'Baliya', 'Agra'],
            correctAnswer: 'Lucknow'
        }
    ]
} 